Robert Adam H<u>inkel</u>

Washington, D.C. Metro Area || C: (240)-351-3522 || AHinkel421@gmail.com Github: https://github.com/ahinkel421 || Portfolio: www.adamhinkel.com

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer transitioning from a financial background to a career in Web Development. Recent graduate and Assistant Instructor of Web Development at Thinkful (Intensive six month Full Stack Web Development Program).

Skills

Front-end: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, ReactJS Back-end: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB/Mongoose

Projects

CloudNine -

A MERN stack app that allows users to share positive experiences, inspirational quotes, or anything to boost the morale of others.

Goalstrive -

A goal oriented task management app where users are able to log in/out and break their larger goals into smaller, more achievable goals.

Zipadopt -

Using the Google Maps and Petfinder APIs, Zipadopt allows users to browse for adoptable pets in their area(s).

Trial-by-trivia -

A fun quiz app that allows fantasy nerds (like myself) to test their Game of Thrones knowledge in a "Trial by Trivia!"

Experience

Thinkful (Independent Contractor) (Washington, D.C.) | June 2017 - Present

Assistant Instructor -

- Oversees/hosts Thinkful's public workshops
- Helps students grasp new technologies such as HTML, CSS, Javascript, and jQuery
- Ensures all students are assisted in a patient, friendly manner

BSI Financial Services (Bethesda, MD) | April 2016 - March 2017

Foreclosure Analyst -

*Greylocke and Company's contract with BSI was terminated in April 2016. 3 of Greylocke and Company's 10 employees were hired, full time.

$\underline{\textbf{Greylocke \& Company} \ (\textbf{contractor on behalf of BSI Financial Services})} \ \ (\textbf{Bethesda, MD}) \ | \ \textit{August 2015 - April 2016} \ | \ \textit{April 2016} \ | \ \textit{April 2016} \ | \ \textit{April 2016} \ | \ \textit{August 2015 - April 2016} \ | \ \textit{April 2016} \ | \ \textit{April$

Foreclosure Analyst -

- Serviced default loans from the date of default through the foreclosure sale
- Managed attorneys to ensure the foreclosure process was being expedited
- Maintained foreclosure statuses in all systems of records used by BSI

Education

Thinkful: Full Stack Web Development Program | May 2017 - December 2017

Web Development || Online/Washington, D.C.

Montgomery College || *September 2011 - May 2013*

General Studies || Rockville, MD